I spread a parasol to keep the heat out.
The long-awaited Obon vacation has begun.
I'm going to spend more time at home.
I bought some flowers.
I'm going to take a break with a cup of buckwheat tea.
Lovely manjuu buns, a souvenir of Shizuoka!
A crunchy, cheery taste.
I bought some cosmetics at the station's general store.
Cool colors.
I bought it to use with my yukata.
I was attracted by the word “beautiful nails”.
It's hot, so I'm going to get ready for a bath.
I want to put them in different places.
I'm going to put them up little by little.
I bought this meat for a samgyeopsal party.
Defrost the meat first.
I'm going to cook some rice.
I chose the scent of the forest to relax.
I chose a body soap with a strong scent because it's summer.
I cook dinner.
Plenty of cabbage.
Asakizuke with 1% salt, salted kelp and chili peppers.
Salted cucumbers are frozen.
I make a green onion salad that goes perfectly with samgyeopsal.
I froze them as a block.
I grill them all.
I make it spicy with gochujang (red pepper paste).
A hot dish.
I didn't have any ingredients.
I dug out some frozen edamame.
It's ready to serve over microwaved tofu.
I just received news of the birth of second baby.
The first child is becoming a big sister. I prepared a card to say 'Congratulations on becoming a big sister!' to her.
Together with tea that brought Mom's face to mind when I tasted it.
She says first child is a little jealous of the baby.
Will the child remember her current feelings as an adult?
I don't remember what it was like to have a sister.🤭
Another happy event in August!
I'm going to make afogado which I saw on instagram with green tea ice cream and red bean paste.
It's an unexpected combination, but it's delicious.
I hide the unevenness of the nails.
I slept well and woke up slowly.
Fried cabbage with a hint of curry.
A little soy sauce.
How to make hot dogs with sliced bread. 🤭
Cold instant soup.
Today's drink is hot coffee with extra hot water.
Curry flavored cabbage was a nice addition.😋
I was soaring this year, wondering if I would have a chance to wear a yukata.🤫
With the help of the video,
I love the time I manage to spend dressing.
I'm wondering about a few things here and there.
I'll let the dark night cheat me.😅
Dancing and watching.
A good time for both.
Come back for more if you need more syrup, said the shaved ice man.🍧
It was a festival with warm atmosphere.😊
I found a nice restaurant nearby and went in.
It was my first experience to dine surrounded by antiques.🔍
It was a wonderful time, both the space and the food!
Before going to bed,
I'm a little hungry.
Thank you for watching to the end